unlockboot.com 2016-12-07

# Privacy Policy

### UnlockBoot.Com Privacy Statement

Privacy of our visitors is very important to us at UnlockBoot.Com. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here's info on what forms of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit UnlockBoot.Com.

### Email Addresses

We completely agree that we will never share your email address with any 3rd party service.

### Log Files

As with many other web sites, we collect and use the info contained in our log files. The data in the log files include your Internet service provider, your IP address, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Firefox, Safari or Google Chrome), the device used to visit us (such as mobile, tablet or pc) the time you visited our website and which pages you visited.

### Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies

UnlockBoot.Com may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to control users' site preferences and ensure the the site is functionality.

### Third Party Cookies

UnlockBoot.Com may also use ad network providers and other service providers, such as Google.com, OfficialiPhoneUnlock and Infolinks, to help present customized content and advertisements on UnlockBoot.Com. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash Player installed.

You can to disable, chose or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

### Links

UnlockBoot.Com frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave UnlockBoot.Com we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [Contact Us](http://www.unlockboot.com/p/contact.html).

_Privacy Policy Last Changes: Jan. 28, 2013_

| November 11, 2016
